Guide to the William Preston Few Records and Papers, 1814 - 1971 and undated (bulk 1911-1940) UA.03.55.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
William Preston Few records and papers
1814-1971 and undated (bulk 1911-1940)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Few, W. P. (William Preston), 1867-1940
UA.03.55.0001
70 Linear Feet 69,000 items
William Preston Few (1867-1940) served as President of Trinity College from 1910-1924, and President of Duke University from 1924-1940. Few came to Trinity College in 1896 as Professor of English, was named Dean of the College in 1902, and President in 1910, succeeding John C. Kilgo. Few worked with James Buchanan Duke to establish the Duke Endowment. In 1924, Few directed Trinity College's transition to Duke University and remained as President of Duke University until his death in 1940. Few was an active layman in the Methodist Church and in the Methodist Episcopal Church, South. The William Preston Few Records and Papers contain correspondence from Few's office files as President of Trinity College and Duke University, reports, clippings, copies of speeches and manuscripts, memorandum books, bound volumes, index cards that catalog Few's office files, and other types of printed material. Major subjects include education; philanthropy; the development of Trinity College from its beginning in Randolph County, N.C., to Duke University; the development of the Duke Endowment; Trinity and Duke departmental operations; the school's relationship with the Methodist Church; and business of the Methodist Episcopal Church, South. English.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
No restrictions except the Clipping File, Folders 1410-1412, is not immediately accessible because it requires further processing before use.
Provenance
The William Preston Few Records and Papers were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1964 (A64-60), with multiple earlier accessions, and later additions (A67-76) and (A72-68).
Biographical Note
Born in Greenville, S.C. on December 29, 1867, the son of Benjamin Franklin and Rachel Kendrick Few, William Preston Few attended Wofford College, Spartanburg S.C. (A.B., 1889), and Harvard University (A.M., 1893; Ph.D., 1896). Few came to Durham in 1896 as Professor of English at Trinity College. He was named Dean of the College in 1902, and President in 1910, succeeding John C. Kilgo. Few was President of Trinity College from 1910-1924.
On August 17, 1911, Few married Mary Reamey Thomas of Martinsville, West Virginia. They had five sons: William, Lyne Starling, Kendrick Sheffield, Randolph Reamey, and Yancey Preston.
Few worked with James Buchanan Duke to establish the Duke Endowment. In 1924, Few directed Trinity College's transition to Duke University and remained as President of Duke University until his death on October 16, 1940. In his thirty years as President of Trinity and Duke, Few oversaw the transformation of Trinity College into Duke University and assisted in the fulfillment of the concept behind the Duke Endowment.
An active layman in the Methodist Church, Few was often a delegate to the Church's General Conferences. Other activities included membership on a committee of the Harvard Board of Overseers (1911), President of the North Carolina Literary and Historical Association (1913), Trustee of the Negro Rural School Fund (1918), and President of the Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (1932).
Collection Overview
The William Preston Few Records and Papers contain correspondence from Few's office files as President of Trinity College and Duke University, reports, clippings, copies of speeches and manuscripts, memorandum books, bound volumes, index cards that catalog Few's office files, and other types of printed material. The files are arranged in six series. They include: Correspondence, Subject Files, Bound Volumes, Oversize Materials, Index Cards to Few Papers, and Additions.
Major subjects include education; philanthropy; the development of Trinity College, from its beginning in Randolph County, N.C., to Duke University; the development of the Duke Endowment; Trinity and Duke departmental operations; the school's relationship with the Methodist Church; and business of the Methodist Episcopal Church, South.
The Correspondence makes up a large part of the collection. The bulk of this correspondence is from Few's office files as President of Trinity College and Duke University. The correspondence includes incoming letters to Few's office, copies of outgoing letters, reports, minutes, telegrams, newsletters, and other materials generated or received by the President's office. Among the correspondents are: William Hayes Ackland, Alice Mary Baldwin, John Spencer Bassett, Julian S. Carr, Robert D.W. Conner, Angier Buchanan Duke, Benjamin Newton Duke, James Buchanan Duke, John Carlisle Kilgo, and Edward R. Murrow. There is also some personal correspondence dating from 1885.
The Subject Files include a wide variety of materials collected by Few's office. They include correspondence, reports, clippings and other types of printed material. Major subjects include education; philanthropy; the development of Trinity College from its beginning in Randolph County, N.C., to Duke University; the development of the Duke Endowment; Trinity and Duke departmental operations; the school's relationship with the Methodist Church; and the Methodist Episcopal Church, South. Included are Few's speeches made at university functions, to community groups, and at funerals. There are a number of speeches that give Few's opinions about education and the development of Duke University while he was President.
The Bound Volumes include a manuscript arithmetic primer, dated 1814, written by Alston W. Kendrick, Few's grandfather; a trigonometry textbook used by Few; a Bible; class records, 1913-1929 and undated; an incomplete set of Few's memoranda books for the years 1922-1933; and several alumni reviews.
The Index Cards to Few's Papers were apparently created by Few's office and catalog the holdings in the office files. However, not all of the materials or names referenced on the index cards can be found in the William Preston Few Records and Papers.
The Oversize Materials include folders removed from the subject files, diplomas, and a bound volume. The Additions include some correspondence, and obituaries for Mrs. William Preston Few (Mary Reamey Thomas Few), that were incorporated into the collection after it was transferred to University Archives.
Related Material
Duke University Board of Trustees Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Duke University Faculty Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
[Forms part of:] Duke University President Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Robert L. Flowers Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Marion Timothy Plyler Papers.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Scrapbook of News Clippings on Dr. William P. Few.
University Archives, Duke University.
William Hane Wannamaker Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Education -- North Carolina; Clippings (information artifacts); Educational fund raising; Universities and colleges -- United States; Few, W. P. (William Preston), 1867-1940; Few, W. P. (William Preston), 1867-1940; Trinity College (Randolph County, N.C.) -- History; Trinity College (Durham, N.C.) -- History; Methodist Episcopal Church, South; Duke University. Presidents; Duke, James Buchanan, 1856-1925; Duke University -- Presidents; Duke University. Board of Trustees; Methodist Church -- North Carolina; Methodist Episcopal Church, South -- Education; Duke University -- Administration; Duke University -- History; Duke Endowment
- Correspondence, 1885-1941 and undated
  Scope and Contents note
  The bulk of the correspondence is from Few's office files as President of Trinity College and Duke University. The correspondence includes incoming letters to Few's office, copies of outgoing letters, reports, minutes, telegrams, newsletters, and other materials generated or received by the President's office. Among the correspondents are: Alice Mary Baldwin, John Carlisle Kilgo, John Spencer Bassett, Angier Buchanan Duke, Benjamin Newton Duke, William Hayes Ackland, Julian S. Carr, Edward R. Murrow, and Robert D.W. Conner. There is also some personal correspondence dating from 1885.
  Duke University Archives staff has created an index to a number of significant correspondents who have letters in the Few Records and Papers. The following people are noted to have significant autograph entries, as well as significant subject entries in this collection, on topics that concern Trinity's and Duke's administration, faculty, and trustees. There is an extensive listing of correspondents for other subject areas including the Methodist Episcopal Church, South; Education; and Philanthropy. Please contact University Archives staff for further information about correspondence related to these topics.
  Allen, George Garland
  Anderson, Albert
  Baldwin, Alice Mary
  Boyd, William Kenneth
  Branscomb, Bennett Harvie
  Brown, Frank Clyde
  Brown, Joseph Gill
  Bruton, John Fletcher
  Cannon, James, III
  Davison, WIlburt Cornell
  Edwards, Charles William
  Ellwood, Charles Abram
  Flowers, Robert Lee
  Glasson, William Henry
  Godbey, Allenn Howard
  McDougall, William
  Miller, Justin
  North, Harry M.
  Peacock, Dred
  Peele, William Walter
  Peppler, Charles William
  Reynolds, William Neal
  Rhine, Joseph Banks
  Separk, Joseph Henry
  Smith, Willis
  Soper, Edmund Davison
  Spence, Hersey Everett
  Toms, Clinton White
  White, Newman Ivey
  - 1885-March 13, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 1-9)
  - March 14-June 30, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 10-20)
  - July-Dec., 1911 (Box 3, Folder 21-33)
  - Jan.-May, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 34-46)
  - June-Sept., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 47-56)
  - Oct., 1912-March, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 57-72)
  - April-Aug., 1913 (Box 7, Folder 73-85)
  - Sept. 1913-Feb., 1914 (Box 8, Folder 86-101)
  - March-July 17, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 102-114)
  - July 18-Dec., 1914 (Box 10, Folder 115-127)
  - Jan.-May, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 128-141)
  - June-Dec., 1915 (Box 12, Folder 142-154)
  - Jan.-May, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 155-167)
  - June-Oct., 1916 (Box 14, Folder 168-180)
  - Nov., 1916-Feb., 1917 (Box 15, Folder 181-191)
  - March-May, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 192-202)
  - June-Aug. 19, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 203-215)
  - Aug. 20-Nov., 1917 (Box 18, Folder 216-227)
  - Dec., 1917-April, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 228-242)
  - May-Sept., 1918 (Box 20, Folder 243-255)
  - Oct., 1918-Feb., 1919 (Box 21, Folder 256-266)
  - March-July, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 267-278)
  - Aug.-Nov., 1919 (Box 23, Folder 279-289)
  - Dec., 1919-March, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 290-299)
  - April-Sept., 1920 (Box 25, Folder 300-310)
  - Oct., 1920-Feb., 1921 (Box 26, Folder 311-322)
  - March-Aug., 1921 (Box 27, Folder 323-334)
  - Sept.-Dec., 1921 (Box 28, Folder 335-346)
  - Jan.-April, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 347-357)
  - May-Sept., 1922 (Box 30, Folder 358-367)
  - Oct., 1922-Jan., 1923 (Box 31, Folder 368-379)
  - Feb.-June, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 380-392)
  - July, 1923-Feb., 1924 (Box 33, Folder 393-402)
  - March-Sept., 1924 (Box 34, Folder 403-416)
  - Oct., 1924-Jan., 1925 (Box 35, Folder 417-430)
  - Feb.-May, 1925 (Box 36, Folder 431-443)
  - June-Sept., 1925 (Box 37, Folder 444-455)
  - Oct.-Dec., 1925 (Box 38, Folder 456-465)
  - Jan.-April, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 466-477)
  - May-Sept., 1926 (Box 40, Folder 478-489)
  - Oct., 1926-Jan., 1927 (Box 41, Folder 490-500)
  - Feb.-April, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 501-511)
  - May-Aug., 1927 (Box 43, Folder 512-522)
  - Sept.-Dec., 1927 (Box 44, Folder 523-533)
  - Jan.-April, 1928 (Box 45, Folder 534-546)
  - May-Aug., 1928 (Box 46, Folder 547-557)
  - Sept.-Nov., 1928 (Box 47, Folder 558-567)
  - Dec., 1928-March, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 568-577)
  - April-July, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 578-589)
  - Aug.-Oct., 1929 (Box 50, Folder 590-599)
  - Nov., 1929-Jan., 1930 (Box 51, Folder 600-608)
  - Feb.-April, 1930 (Box 52, Folder 609-617)
  - May-Aug., 1930 (Box 53, Folder 618-626)
  - Sept.-Oct., 1930 (Box 54, Folder 627-634)
  - Nov., 1930-Jan. 19, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 635-642)
  - Jan. 20-March 18, 1931 (Box 56, Folder 643-650)
  - March 19-May 17, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 651-661)
  - May 18-Aug., 1931 (Box 58, Folder 662-671)
  - Sept.-Nov. 21, 1931 (Box 59, Folder 672-680)
  - Nov. 23, 1931-Jan., 1932 (Box 60, Folder 681-691)
  - Feb.-March, 1932 (Box 61, Folder 692-702)
  - April-May, 1932 (Box 62, Folder 703-713)
  - June-Sept. 9, 1932 (Box 63, Folder 714-722)
  - Sept. 10-Nov., 1932 (Box 64, Folder 723-733)
  - Dec., 1932-Jan., 1933 (Box 65, Folder 734-742)
  - Feb.-April 20, 1933 (Box 66, Folder 743-750)
  - April 21-June, 1933 (Box 67, Folder 751-757)
  - July-Sept., 1933 (Box 68, Folder 758-766)
  - Oct.-Dec. 12, 1933 (Box 69, Folder 767-776)
  - Dec. 13, 1933-Feb. 15, 1934 (Box 70, Folder 777-785)
  - Feb. 16-April 16, 1934 (Box 71, Folder 786-795)
  - April 17-June, 1934 (Box 72, Folder 796-806)
  - July-Sept. 20, 1934 (Box 73, Folder 807-817)
  - Sept. 21-Nov., 1934 (Box 74, Folder 818-828)
  - Dec., 1934-Feb. 16, 1935 (Box 75, Folder 829-838)
  - Feb. 18-April 12, 1935 (Box 76, Folder 839-847)
  - April 13-June 12, 1935 (Box 77, Folder 848-857)
  - June 13-Aug., 1935 (Box 78, Folder 858-868)
  - Sept.-Nov. 9, 1935 (Box 79, Folder 869-878)
  - Nov. 10, 1935-Jan. 10, 1936 (Box 80, Folder 879-886)
  - Jan. 11-March 16, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 887-895)
  - March 17-May 18, 1936 (Box 82, Folder 896-905)
  - May 19-July, 1936 (Box 83, Folder 906-914)
  - Aug.-Oct. 18, 1936 (Box 84, Folder 915-924)
  - Oct. 19-Dec. 15, 1936 (Box 85, Folder 925-932)
  - Dec. 16, 1936-Feb., 1937 (Box 86, Folder 933-943)
  - March-May 21, 1937 (Box 87, Folder 944-952)
  - May 22-Aug., 1937 (Box 88, Folder 953-962)
  - Sept.-Oct., 1937 (Box 89, Folder 963-970)
  - Nov., 1937-Jan. 24, 1938 (Box 90, Folder 971-980)
  - Jan. 25-March, 1938 (Box 91, Folder 981-990)
  - April-May, 1938 (Box 92, Folder 991-998)
  - June-Sept. 18, 1938 (Box 93, Folder 999-1007)
  - Sept. 19-Nov. 10, 1938 (Box 94, Folder 1008-1016)
  - Nov. 11-Jan. 11, 1939 (Box 95, Folder 1017-1025)
  - Jan. 12-March 15, 1939 (Box 96, Folder 1026-1035)
  - March 16-May 17, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 1036-1045)
  - May 18-Aug. 14, 1939 (Box 98, Folder 1046-1053)
  - Aug. 15-Oct. 25, 1939 (Box 99, Folder 1054-1062)
  - Oct. 26-Dec., 1939 (Box 100, Folder 1063-1070)
  - Jan.-Feb., 1940 (Box 101, Folder 1071-1078)
  - March-May 13, 1940 (Box 102, Folder 1079-1087)
  - May 14-Aug. 25, 1940 (Box 103, Folder 1088-1097)
  - Aug. 26-Nov., 1940 (Box 104, Folder 1098-1107)
  - Dec. 3, 1940-Nov. 30, 1941, and undated (Box 105, Folder 1108-1109)
- Subject Files
  The subject files include a wide variety of materials collected by the Few's office. They include correspondence, reports, clippings and other types of printed material. Major subjects include education; philanthropy; the development of Trinity College, from its beginning in Randolph County, NC, to Duke University; the development of the Duke Endowment; Trinity and Duke departmental operations; the school's relationship with the Methodist Church; and the Methodist Episcopal Church, South.
  The subseries on Few's speeches and writings is significant. The major subjects covered in this section include the development of Duke University, the role of religion in education, student development, and the contributions of the Duke family to education. Included are speeches Few made at university functions, to community groups, and at funerals. Some of the materials are organized by date, or by topic. There are a number of undated speeches, on a wide variety of topics, that mostly give Few's opinions about education and the development of Duke University while he was president.
  The subject files include a wealth of material on Trinity College, the establishment of the Duke Endowment in 1924, and the transformation of Trinity into an undergraduate college of Duke University. Of note is a printer's proof from the Durham Herald of the first headline to use the term, Duke University. Also included in the Subject Files are President's Reports; records of committees of the Methodist Episcopal Church, South; correspondence concerning the institution's relationship to the Methodist Church; and histories of Union Institute and Normal College. Certain materials received by the President's office in the course of business may have been considered important enough to warrant the attention of the Board of Trustees; thus, some records of the President's Office will be found in the Board's records.
  - Ackland, William Hayes (Box 106, Folder 1110-1111)
  - Alliance for Guidance of Rural Youth (Box 106, Folder 1112)
  - American Association of Junior Colleges (Box 106, Folder 1113)
  - American Council On Education (Box 106, Folder 1114)
  - Association Of American Colleges (Box 106, Folder 1115-1116)
  - Association Of American Medical Colleges (Box 106, Folder 1117)
  - Athens, American University of, 1937 (Box 106, Folder 1118)
  - Cole (E.M.) Foundation (Box 106, Folder 1119)
  - Duke, Angier Buchanan (Box 106, Folder 1120)
  - Duke, Benjamin Newton (Box 106, Folder 1121)
  - Duke, James Buchanan
    - Last Will And Testament (Box 106, Folder 1122)
    - Superannuate Fund
      - Dec., 1916-Dec., 1917 (Box 106, Folder 1123)
      - Dec., 1918-Dec., 1919 (Box 106, Folder 1124)
      - Dec., 1920-Dec., 1921 (Box 107, Folder 1125)
      - Dec., 19, 1922-Dec., 1923 (Box 107, Folder 1126)
      - Dec., 1934-Dec., 1935 (Box 107, Folder 1127)
      - Dec., 1936-Dec., 1937 (Box 107, Folder 1128)
      - Dec., 1938-Dec., 1939 (Box 107, Folder 1129)
  - Duke Endowment
    - General Information (Box 107, Folder 1130)
    - Hospital and Orphan Section (Box 107, Folder 1131)
    - Rural Church Fund (Box 107, Folder 1132-1133)
  - Duke Memorial (Box 107, Folder 1134)
  - Duke Memorial Methodist Church (Box 107, Folder 1135)
  - Duke University (Box 108)
    Few was President of Duke University from 1924-1940. Many important changes in the structure and implementation of the university's educational goals occurred during this time. Major subjects include university development; departmental business; the development of the Forestry School, the Law School; the Medical Center; various aspects of student life; and building on campus.
    - Architecture (Box 108, Folder 1136)
    - Attendance Regulations (Box 108, Folder 1137)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 108, Folder 1138-1139)
    - Bulletin (Box 108, Folder 1140)
    - Centennial Celebration (Box 108, Folder 1141-1142)
    - Chanticleer (Box 108, Folder 1143)
    - Chapel Committee, 1936-1938 (Box 108, Folder 1144)
    - Chapel Sermons (Box 108, Folder 1145)
    - Chemistry Dept. (Box 108, Folder 1146)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 108, Folder 1147)
    - Curriculum, 1936 (Box 108, Folder 1148)
    - Committee on the Promotion of Student Scholarship, 1936-1937 (Box 108, Folder 1149)
    - Degree Requirements (Box 108, Folder 1150)
    - Engineering Division (Box 109, Folder 1151-1152)
    - English Dept. (Box 109, Folder 1153)
    - Faculty Committees (Box 109, Folder 1154-1155)
    - Forestry School (Box 109, Folder 1156)
    - Flowers Collection (Box 109, Folder 1157)
    - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 109, Folder 1158)
    - Freshman Advisory Council (Box 109, Folder 1159)
    - Graduate School (Box 109, Folder 1160)
    - Historical Material (Box 110, Folder 1161)
      Includes a printer's proof from the Durham Herald of the first headline to use the term, Duke University.
    - Honors Courses (Box 110, Folder 1162)
    - Jewish Students (Box 110, Folder 1163)
    - The Vision of King Paucus, [1933?] (Box 110, Folder 1164)
      A one-act play in three scenes.
    - Law School (Box 110, Folder 1165-1166)
    - Medical Center (Box 110, Folder 1167-1168)
    - Men's Student Government Association (Box 110, Folder 1169)
    - Miscellaneous Duke University Material (Box 110, Folder 1170)
    - Names of Buildings (Box 110, Folder 1171)
    - Philosophy Dept. (Box 110, Folder 1172)
    - Physical Education for Men (Box 110, Folder 1173)
    - Physical Education for Women (Box 110, Folder 1174)
    - Physics Dept. (Box 110, Folder 1175)
    - President's Report (Box 110, Folder 1176)
    - Printed Material (Box 111, Folder 1177)
    - Program of Cooperation with the University of N.C. (Box 111, Folder 1178)
    - Report on the Administration of the Curriculum (Box 111, Folder 1179)
    - Research Committee
      - 1931 (Box 111, Folder 1180)
      - 1932 (Box 111, Folder 1181)
    - Rural Church Institute (Box 111, Folder 1182)
    - Sabbatical Leave (Box 111, Folder 1183)
    - School of Religion (Box 111, Folder 1184)
    - Social Sciences (Box 111, Folder 1185)
    - Social Science Research Institute (Box 111, Folder 1186)
    - Sociology Dept. (Box 111, Folder 1187)
    - Statistics (Box 111, Folder 1188)
    - Student Health Dept. (Box 111, Folder 1189)
    - Student Life Division (Box 111, Folder 1190)
    - Student Publications Council (Box 111, Folder 1191)
    - Student Religious Activities (Box 111, Folder 1192)
    - Student Revolt of 1934 (Box 112, Folder 1193)
    - Summer School (Box 112, Folder 1194)
    - Tuition Fees (Box 112, Folder 1195)
    - Undergraduate Curriculum Committee (Box 112, Folder 1196)
    - Duke University Day (Box 112, Folder 1197)
    - Woman's College (Box 112, Folder 1198)
    - Zoology Dept. (Box 112, Folder 1199)
  - Duke University Press (Box 112, Folder 1200)
  - Duke, Washington. Monument (Box 112, Folder 1201)
  - Durham Shakespeare Tercentenary Celebration (Box 112, Folder 1202)
  - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars (Box 112, Folder 1203)
  - Emory University (Box 112, Folder 1204)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America (Box 112, Folder 1205)
  - Few, Ellie (Box 112, Folder 1206)
  - Few, Mary Reamey Thomas (Box 112, Folder 1207)
  - Few, William Preston
    - Baccalaureate Addresses, 1931-1940 (Box 112, Folder 1208)
    - Biographical and Genealogical Material (Box 112, Folder 1209)
    - Death of William Preston Few (Box 112, Folder 1210-1211)
    - Inauguration as President of Trinity College, 1910 (Box 113, Folder 1212-1213)
    - Twentieth Anniversary as President (Box 113, Folder 1214)
      Includes newspaper clippings.
    - Speeches, Writings, and Lecture Notes, 1910-1940 and undated
      The major subjects covered in this section include the development of Duke University, the role of religion in education, student development, and the contributions of the Duke family to education. Included are speeches Few made at university functions, to community groups, and at funerals. Some of the materials are organized by date or by topic. There are a number of undated speeches on a wide variety of topics that mostly give Few's opinions about education and the development of Duke University while he was President.
      - Speeches, Writings, and Lecture Notes, 1910-1927 (Box 113, Folder 1215-1216)
      - How Education and Religion Can Work Together, 1929 (Box 113, Folder 1217)
      - Speeches, Writings, and Lecture Notes, 1928-1931 (Box 113, Folder 1218-1219)
      - Speeches, Writings, and Lecture Notes, 1932-1933 (Box 113, Folder 1220-1221)
      - Writings on Trinity, Duke, and Education, 1933-1939 and undated (Box 114, Folder 1222)
      - Speeches, Writings, and Lecture Notes, 1934-1935 (Box 114, Folder 1223)
      - Speeches, Writings, and Lecture Notes, 1936-1938 (Box 114, Folder 1224)
      - Speeches, Writings, and Lecture Notes, 1939-1940 (Box 114, Folder 1225-1226)
      - Education, Funeral Eulogies, Duke Family, and other topics (Box 114, Folder 1227)